{"data":{"createNewExamAttempt":{"attempt":{"id":"0b073a91-3c6f-4c14-b248-b50801623228"},"exam":{"id":"0cdc0d27-081b-4e73-84b6-580722d1469a","title":"AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Exam","duration":5400,"totalQuestions":65,"questions":[{"id":"b7d5jc0p-zg8y-0hwp-3cjv-2yxp349xk58p","domain":"security","question":"You want to streamline access management for your AWS administrators by assigning them a pre-defined set of permissions based on their job role - which of the below is the best way to approach this?","explanation":"Using IAM Groups lets you create a list of pre-defined permissions that any user made a part of that group will be granted. Roles are primarily used to grant AWS resources permissions to other AWS resources and generally are not for end-users. Amazon Cognito is a service that help authenticate users to your apps, and not the AWS console itself.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_groups.html","title":"IAM Groups"}],"answers":[{"id":"28639700aadbc704e3daae5ba44ab388","text":"Use Amazon Cognito","correct":false},{"id":"48fb6d39f4c7857dc342d789480a20ea","text":"Use AWS Organizations","correct":false},{"id":"ffc1a593680549bf1bc0e966a70f0683","text":"Use IAM Groups","correct":true},{"id":"71f7b94ac76ec4aa2860353bc1120591","text":"Use IAM Roles","correct":false}]},{"id":"8ae68d9e-7bf8-41c2-996a-a01fb1bf966a","domain":"billing","question":"Which tool can help you to compare the cost of hosting resources in AWS vs the cost of hosting in a traditional data centre?","explanation":"The TCO calculators allow you to estimate the cost savings when using AWS and provide a detailed set of reports.  Pricing Calculator can be used to estimate potential AWS spend, and AWS Budgets & Billing Alarms can help keep spend under control by alerting you when you breach a threshold.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/tco-calculator/","title":"AWS TCO Calculator"}],"answers":[{"id":"6b6f2097ec6555c2e09b7ed23571b3c5","text":"AWS Billing Alarms","correct":false},{"id":"e84e1dd83afcda636af8a6ae32a58cef","text":"AWS TCO Calculator","correct":true},{"id":"e32a801c8e0beab6abb9361e937365be","text":"AWS Budgets","correct":false},{"id":"1a98a10ad310a9ed66414dd3acb48e72","text":"AWS Pricing Calculator","correct":false}]},{"id":"123bb9de-8d93-4feb-81c0-d4e85038cd47","domain":"tech","question":"When setting up the properties of an S3 bucket, which of the following options should you select to get detailed records for the requests made to the bucket?","explanation":"Server access logging is what you should select to record and get information on the requests made to your bucket. Object-level logging, sometimes referred to as S3 CloudTrail logging, saves all API events performed on the S3 bucket in json format.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/ServerLogs.html","title":"Amazon S3 Server Access Logging"}],"answers":[{"id":"30054ccc9b587d53668a89942396874c","text":"Server access logging","correct":true},{"id":"189f63f277cd73395561651753563065","text":"Tags","correct":false},{"id":"f87d839acefa86eff3c90b1b44be4aba","text":"Object-level logging","correct":false},{"id":"198a30920479d1d8e2509b9b59f3d700","text":"Versioning","correct":false}]},{"id":"8x0x6jdm-e0n1-0rb6-ibad-we2hbkuaxgvw","domain":"tech","question":"You need to store a collection of objects that can also be accessed from a different AWS Region. Which service should you use to do this?","explanation":"S3 allows you to access objects from anywhere in the world - as long as the appropriate permissions are set!","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/Welcome.html","title":"About S3"}],"answers":[{"id":"6ebb7423072c5943f52c11274fd71b0b","text":"DynamoDB","correct":false},{"id":"e66f7962b812129e4a3890b1dab122c0","text":"Elastic Container Service","correct":false},{"id":"248c1b0bcb74394beb4a08030c4a6847","text":"EBS","correct":false},{"id":"e2ab7c65b21ed8cc1c3b642b5e36429e","text":"S3","correct":true}]},{"id":"mlqp7x88-xfgl-3xkm-trto-wx59uhf7dox6","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the below allows you to restrict access to individual objects in an S3 bucket? ","explanation":"Access Control Lists let you control access to individual objects within an S3 bucket, whereas Bucket Policies allow you to control access to entire buckets. In relation to S3, Bucket Control Lists and Access Policies do not exist as configuration items.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/using-iam-policies.html","title":"About S3 Bucket Policies"}],"answers":[{"id":"64d03326bddfa39f7ae9a129e8b731c6","text":"Bucket Access Lists","correct":false},{"id":"303a25c2935ec1fdb01208b6f4f65688","text":"Access Control Lists","correct":true},{"id":"7cfde5ee620a2532233ca18a68fd35ba","text":"Bucket Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"8eaf761b0344c54cfcf063cb006e4ad1","text":"Access Policies","correct":false}]},{"id":"zlyf2s8s-kula-sxtl-s07a-i3uh455n1hnu","domain":"security","question":"Which credentials can you use to access the AWS Management console?","explanation":"You use a username and password to log into the AWS console, although Access key and Secret Access key can be used to access some APIs programmatically","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/console/","title":"The AWS Management Console"}],"answers":[{"id":"4dd4dfb52929ef230415ada1a4169dc1","text":"Your Security Token","correct":false},{"id":"be677306ceb7d966e7a06ee1bf387acf","text":"Your Access key","correct":false},{"id":"afc76c6d8222878e0449abb2ea16838f","text":"Your Username and Password","correct":true},{"id":"2a7454c71a60c06ab2189283f1788e09","text":"Your Secret Access key","correct":false}]},{"id":"ca0mnlws-zcum-4ktx-vhea-4j7tzi5qof7m","domain":"security","question":"What is the recommended way to give your applications running in EC2 permission to other AWS resources?","explanation":"You should use IAM Roles wherever possible to enable applications running on EC2 instances to access other AWS resources. This is the most secure method to do so. It is not possible to assign an IAM Group or User to an instance, and although using the Root Keys in you application would work this is HIGHLY insecure and should never be done, as the Root Keys have access to absolutely everything in your account.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/iam-roles-for-amazon-ec2.html","title":"IAM Roles for Amazon EC2"}],"answers":[{"id":"d12b50f23d2457b811312e994c2569d0","text":"Create an IAM User with appropriate permissions and assign it to the instance.","correct":false},{"id":"6bd8f4a2aff7022a330dc33c097a2f5a","text":"Create an IAM Role with appropriate permissions and assign it to the instance.","correct":true},{"id":"0bce771e576c7cf6bd90b9463d344860","text":"Create an IAM Group with appropriate permissions and assign it to the instance.","correct":false},{"id":"01943125f389f038045d6c0c56cafcce","text":"Create an Root Access Key and use it in the application.","correct":false}]},{"id":"57f5e909-774f-43b9-9718-c0b61fc8225c","domain":"security","question":"You are currently running an application in a production environment, but you want to ensure that it is free of vulnerabilities. Which of the following AWS services would you need to use?","explanation":"You will need to turn to Amazon Inspector for security assessment. Not only does it identify vulnerabilities in your application, it will also spot deviations from security best practices. AWS Shield and WAF protect the application from attacks that exploit vulnerabilities, rather than identify them. And Trusted Advisor only provides recommendations on how to improve security.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/inspector/latest/userguide/inspector_introduction.html","title":"What is Amazon Inspector?"}],"answers":[{"id":"543096643aa6d28d9fac278e9257783d","text":"Amazon Inspector","correct":true},{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":false},{"id":"41a831f771ef9bece59ed5160e335ae7","text":"AWS Trusted Inspector","correct":false},{"id":"769f2c629067645d4b60e13009500c9f","text":"AWS Web Application Firewall (WAF)","correct":false}]},{"id":"1978e26b-04e4-45ca-8a47-205e50d96c7f","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the below is correct when looking at Regions, Availability Zones, Edge Location and Datacentres?","explanation":"Regions contain two or more Availability Zones, which are themselves made up of one or more Datacentres. Edge locations are a part of AWS' content distribution network, and are seperate from Regions and AZs.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regions_az/?p=ngi&loc=2","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"988326895b235b7a5f2b7eea1a9838f5","text":"Regions contain Availability Zones","correct":true},{"id":"23b72701776466936b717d47eb3be164","text":"Availability Zones contain Data Centres","correct":true},{"id":"22d0cb7092012aea1123fcbd58c6519c","text":"Data Centres contain Availability Zones","correct":false},{"id":"cd6f4614de9281b97b511a1f3f534e8c","text":"Edge Locations contain Availability Zones","correct":false}]},{"id":"11cddf60-2bb5-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following AWS services is an example of Platform as a Service?","explanation":"Platform as a Service, or PaaS, enables the development, running, and management of applications on the cloud without the need to build and maintain any infrastructure. That is precisely what Elastic Beanstalk provides; the ability to quickly deploy and manage applications in the AWS Cloud without worrying about the infrastructure that runs those applications. Elastic Beanstalk is the only PaaS listed here.","links":[{"url":"https: //aws.amazon.com/elasticbeanstalk/","title":"AWS Elastic Beanstalk"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/types-of-cloud-computing/","title":"Types of Cloud Computing"}],"answers":[{"id":"dee7ff8f7b10b9d388c7c561e9413b0d","text":"AWS Lambda","correct":false},{"id":"c33dcb724e4d74e54dbc8347d4402690","text":"Amazon Virtual Private Cloud","correct":false},{"id":"270fcb785810d0206945029bb05f4e97","text":"Amazon S3","correct":false},{"id":"bcf6eb183b7da148701bcc059a34675f","text":"AWS Elastic Beanstalk","correct":true}]},{"id":"1638290e-2fb4-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following does AWS use to notify you by email when you exceed 85% of your Free Tier limits for each service?","explanation":"AWS uses Budgets to notify you when you exceed 85% of your Free Tier limits for each service you’re using by sending you an email. Picking Cost Explorer as the answer is misleading; it is actually a visualizer you can use to analyze your spend, but it does not alert you on your Free Tier usage. Organizations centralizes the management of your resources; it has nothing to do with usage alerts. And Personal Health Dashboard allows you to visualize the status, rather than usage, of your resources.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/tracking-free-tier-usage.html","title":"Tracking Your Free Tier Usage"}],"answers":[{"id":"c7f176d72688fd87853e31b84159d541","text":"AWS Cost Explorer","correct":false},{"id":"d189bb1b260dc3da48b6e6f5e1ec6879","text":"AWS Personal Health Dashboard","correct":false},{"id":"e32a801c8e0beab6abb9361e937365be","text":"AWS Budgets","correct":true},{"id":"b1820ee1cf68e2e65f263ff7bb207626","text":"AWS Organizations","correct":false}]},{"id":"00f56002-e145-4ed1-94f4-c041d0edd78f","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following is a correct S3 bucket name?","explanation":"Bucket names must start with a lowercase letter or number and must not contain uppercase characters or underscores. 2nd-headquarters-imgs is the only bucket name listed here that adheres to these rules and restrictions.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev//BucketRestrictions.html#bucketnamingrules","title":"Rules for Bucket Naming"}],"answers":[{"id":"5d54f4723cb2118e1da2a67a7628f77d","text":"https://s3.amazonaws.com/2nd_Headquarters_imgs","correct":false},{"id":"5457bb8e9a20209e28f939482cbf590c","text":"https://s3.amazonaws.com/Headquartersimg","correct":false},{"id":"50ccd1e352082b9d31184e260c3830ef","text":"https://s3.amazonaws.com/Second-headquarters-imgs","correct":false},{"id":"2b56c4f3ee0c03e44e37656e651fafcf","text":"https://s3.amazonaws.com/2nd-headquarters-imgs","correct":true}]},{"id":"bd8ac490-21fe-451e-a3e6-6dfa221fb389","domain":"concepts","question":"Deploying your EC2 instances across multiple AZs will help address which Cloud Concept?","explanation":"Having resources across multiple AZ is one way to design for High Availability - the concept that your services in cloud should be designed to tolerate failures in the underlying cloud infrastructure. AWS allows you to do this by providing Availability Zones - each one is independent from the others, and a failure in one should not impact the others. Therefore, if you deploy your application in 2 instances in 2 AZs, and one of the AZs fails, you will still have 1 instance running your application. Automation relates simplifying common repeated tasks and removing the human element. Although scaleability and elasticity (the ability to increase resources according to needs and the ability to go up and down in resources as needed) look like they might fit, as we are talking specifically about Multiple AZs in the question High Availability is the more correct answer","links":[],"answers":[{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":true},{"id":"caea8340e2d186a540518d08602aa065","text":"Automation","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":false},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false}]},{"id":"xun4oj55-ptum-ekl7-y5ot-pqhc5t5psvxi","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following support plans features unlimited (customer-side) contacts and unlimited support cases?","explanation":"Both Enterprise and Business support plans feature unlimited (customer-side) contacts and unlimited support cases.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true}]},{"id":"rbmak3ks-m1is-jjm6-oc1s-77yv6l2wutv1","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the below methods can you use to interact with Glacier?.","explanation":"You can interact with Glacier using the RESTful Glacier web service, the Java or .NET SDKs, or by using Amazon S3 Lifecycle Policies. CloudFormation control of Glacier is currently limited to invoking Lifecycle Policies. ","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/glacier/developer-resources/","title":"Amazon Glacier Resources"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/cli/latest/reference/glacier/index.html","title":"Amazon Glacier - CLI Resources"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSCloudFormation/latest/UserGuide/aws-properties-s3-bucket.html","title":"Amazon Glacier in CloudFormation"}],"answers":[{"id":"5e40757e0ff52b4597ed3d7dae5905a2","text":"The RESTful Glacier web service","correct":true},{"id":"3e0049528ad7f75cce804b2f42daf046","text":"CloudFormation templates","correct":false},{"id":"89dcebe9882f4d2a6ea3c2ca0cbb145e","text":"The AWS CLI","correct":true},{"id":"e3153137238990b012fd6a2885e6793b","text":"The Java or .NET SDKs","correct":true},{"id":"64508034a3d69411b8f69baa321fe661","text":"Amazon S3 Lifecycle Policies","correct":true}]},{"id":"8ilibd7u-7ml9-492r-etu0-n4zubf409ykt","domain":"tech","question":"Amazon Lightsail is an example of which of the following?","explanation":"Lightsail is AWS' Platform-as-a-Service (PaaS) offering - this means that when using Lightsail you don't need to worry about all the components that are required to deliver the Instance such as storage, data, and instance size as AWS manages all that for you. Amazon Lightsail takes away many of the complexities of managing an Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS) solution, like some of the networking. This can also be a drawback, if you want to have a highly configurable service. Since Lightsail lets you run a variety of fully-features applications, it is neither a Software as a Service (SaaS), nor Function as a Service (FaaS) offering ","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/lightsail/","title":"About Lightsail"}],"answers":[{"id":"f53d5c67ce1a2058f77a32af9a7d0c66","text":"Functions as a Service","correct":false},{"id":"0fdc9e547679a07630645143e79cce26","text":"Infrastructure as a Service","correct":false},{"id":"68c0c53c6a8ab47f4b611dbf1c347a26","text":"Software as a Service","correct":false},{"id":"8f637a063500ec391f887ff70bda5f30","text":"Platform as a Service","correct":true}]},{"id":"aabc59b3-b883-454e-8336-dac6f49eb7c3","domain":"security","question":"You are a Systems Administrator who has just started adding IAM users to your company’s AWS account. However, you worry that the users will not create passwords strong enough to prevent unauthorized access. What is the most reliable way to ensure that users are using strong passwords?","explanation":"Use Identity and Access Management (IAM) to apply an IAM password policy. While awareness and training are critical to developing good security practices, the most reliable option is to use an IAM Password Policy, which won't allow users to use lower strength passwords.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_credentials_passwords_account-policy.html?icmpid=docs_iam_console","title":"Setting an Account Password Policy for IAM Users"}],"answers":[{"id":"a08ccc3650b327c02cd13367d8ffa875","text":"Hold an AWS webinar to stress the importance of creating strong passwords.","correct":false},{"id":"6cb5679faafdf0c247c2543bdca0e635","text":"Apply an IAM password policy to ensure users create appropriately strong passwords.","correct":true},{"id":"2ef38712519600d72d012e44a6dcb5a3","text":"Ask for the password of each user and create a much stronger one by yourself.","correct":false},{"id":"da197ad4fa2d98027feab02afd84d7fc","text":"Speak with each IAM user individually about the importance of creating strong passwords.","correct":false}]},{"id":"ef918c09-219a-45b3-b1cc-f5b02cdbfc1d","domain":"concepts","question":"What type of placement group should you use to spread Amazon EC2 instances across logical partitions so that they don’t share the same underlying hardware?","explanation":"With a partition placement group, EC2 instances are placed into logical segments called partitions, each of which has its own set of racks to supply its network and power source. This level of isolation is designed to prevent the impact of hardware failure within your application.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/placement-groups.html","title":"Placement Groups"}],"answers":[{"id":"249694a485fc5d3289c38986b4f8e887","text":"Cluster","correct":false},{"id":"180bc3b1c5619aaef40e803f49921012","text":"Spread","correct":false},{"id":"66f9c6c5b672ee16deeef6e4503cb4bc","text":"Reserve","correct":false},{"id":"3349300356cb3141ea939dcbdf749789","text":"Partition","correct":true}]},{"id":"0mdd9dnl-ji3o-hjum-lyr4-wtpoks65v0z9","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following statements about AWS Region is true?","explanation":"A region is a geographical area divided into Availability Zones. Each region contains at least two publicly accessible Availability Zones.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"1c52cae4b07ea355b6bf0d1522efc7e7","text":"Regions are made up of Availability Zones","correct":true},{"id":"2cf30d8c571fe080cdd53d0a78db5689","text":"Regions are automatically fully synchronized to contain the same data globally","correct":false},{"id":"fddc13d769887bc62fc14c8d844e1aa9","text":"Regions are generally specific geographical areas","correct":true},{"id":"bec481a5e2c63bfc93d4922d5845bd2b","text":"Regions are only available in some locations globally","correct":false}]},{"id":"ipqdbu85-0egr-7f6l-daqk-ftz6657spa8l","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following best describes a system that is always online — without the need for human intervention?","explanation":"A highly available system is one that is always online — without the need for human intervention. Although Fault Tolerance is closely related to High Availability, FT usually implies a degradation of service without human intervention, unlike HA which is like-for-like.","links":[{"url":"https://media.amazonwebservices.com/architecturecenter/AWS_ac_ra_ftha_04.pdf","title":"Fault Tolerance and High Availability Infographic"}],"answers":[{"id":"9818cb0bfa2dfb200a8c078b1fe1c2fd","text":"Highly Available","correct":true},{"id":"35d7975974b40518da5e7f990c6a7d1d","text":"Fault Tolerant","correct":false},{"id":"a078ed5ade8df4aac54efbdb57e63ad2","text":"Elastic","correct":false},{"id":"28cb2468ce3a85b4d10668ec48f5e4d6","text":"Scalable","correct":false}]},{"id":"32c7f1bb-425d-4d33-b870-b88f89ef9f08","domain":"security","question":"An oil and gas utility company which is highly regulated must create a cloud governance scheme. The company is organized into multiple autonomous departments which will all be using AWS resources. These departments each sponsor independent projects that are reviewed by regulatory boards for the approval of customer price increases. The code and infrastructure for each project has production, development, and testing environments. Which of the following account strategies will maximize security and operational efficiency for the company?","explanation":"A multi-layered account structure will work best for this company, leveraging AWS Organizations to establish Organizational Units for each department, and separate production, development, and testing environments. While there is no physical AWS account at the department level, Service Control Policies can be applied at the Organizational Unit level, and billing can be reported separately for each department. An account for each department, in which the department combines dev/test/and prod, or a single account for the company hosting all workloads together will NOT provide for segregation of production, development, and testing environments at the account level. Multiple standalone accounts for each department and environment would compromise operational efficiency in managing environments across departments as there is no overarching AWS Organization to manage all the accounts centrally.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/Security/AWS_Security_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"AWS Security Best Practices"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/organizations/","title":"AWS Organizations"}],"answers":[{"id":"6773420477c1653d8837f13bfa8ec24d","text":"Create a single AWS account for centralized security management","correct":false},{"id":"bb38e2c475c21f60a71674d4dd27ff93","text":"Create multiple AWS accounts, one for each autonomous department within the company","correct":false},{"id":"281f961ca6e4d83f6570979548ba64e2","text":"Create multiple AWS accounts, one for the production environment, one for the development environment, and one for the testing environment for all departments","correct":false},{"id":"e4be6081f1a5dc1cc67c1a4633121580","text":"Create an Organization Unit structure in AWS Organizations with separate underlying accounts for production, development, and testing environments","correct":true}]},{"id":"3edc2ffd-d684-4cf1-83f9-b782b6782711","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following pricing models are available for EC2?","explanation":"EC2 has four different pricing models, On Demand, Reserved, Spot and Dedicated Hosts. Each pricing model has been created for different workload types and use cases.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"acbe4e201e8e2ac67830983f9c8d7970","text":"Dedicated Hosts","correct":true},{"id":"abf84cb49aaf1ec8157f80e4d27d011e","text":"Hybrid Instances","correct":false},{"id":"a687560297f056cb18ffb527b46f79b4","text":"Dot Instances","correct":false},{"id":"244492cdce9dce0555c52ebe1182e0a3","text":"On Demand","correct":true},{"id":"942d4e37dd5607ab68e54755540d4a47","text":"Reserved","correct":true}]},{"id":"vsrs40em-06ny-u7sl-hdn2-xstt497klvo3","domain":"concepts","question":"Generally speaking, what is the minimum number of Availability Zones per AWS Region?","explanation":"At least 2 Availability Zones will be publicly available per AWS Region, with most regions having 3 Availability Zones available. There are specific exceptions to this rule, such as the Osaka Local Region, which has only one AZ by design.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"c4ca4238a0b923820dcc509a6f75849b","text":"1","correct":false},{"id":"c81e728d9d4c2f636f067f89cc14862c","text":"2","correct":true},{"id":"eccbc87e4b5ce2fe28308fd9f2a7baf3","text":"3","correct":false},{"id":"a87ff679a2f3e71d9181a67b7542122c","text":"4","correct":false}]},{"id":"b04194cb-7c18-41fd-af07-af547fcdf3df","domain":"security","question":"A consulting firm is conducting a Sarbanes-Oxley compliance audit of your IT operations. The auditor requests visibility to logs of event history across your AWS-based employee expense system infrastructure. Which AWS service will record and provide give you the information you need?","explanation":"AWS CloudTrail provides visibility to API call activity for AWS infrastructure and other services. AWS Cloudwatch Logs might be part of a centralized logging solution, but all API event information will come from CloudTrail. AWS Systems Manager can process EC2 logs only, and AWS Compliance Manager is not a service offered by AWS.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/cloudtrail/?nc2=h_m1","title":"AWS CloudTrail"}],"answers":[{"id":"113b1ad9ce6cdc3a37ad8475bc9bb2b2","text":"AWS Systems Manager","correct":false},{"id":"28408acf54ab04fe847fd24957e528d9","text":"AWS CloudWatch Logs","correct":false},{"id":"26ca9b29af36f84c577a85a80a58a381","text":"AWS CloudTrail","correct":true},{"id":"811708e04896b95951b61e58635cc92d","text":"AWS Compliance Manager","correct":false}]},{"id":"464c8f56-20a3-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following types of EC2 instances is ideal for workloads that process large data sets in memory?","explanation":"True to its naming, memory optimized instances are specifically for workloads that require more memory than usual to process data.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/instance-types/","title":"Amazon EC2 Instance Types"}],"answers":[{"id":"b26f852f8cf53bd055d76deddcadf155","text":"Compute Optimized","correct":false},{"id":"fb152ac1edfe96da5fe255e395003b0d","text":"Memory Optimized","correct":true},{"id":"ea999a66bf3ccfec4616d5be49348665","text":"Storage Optimized","correct":false},{"id":"94a1a3953054d8ece597f4f69bb343d4","text":"General Purpose","correct":false},{"id":"2f925ef0b67b13f124d684b4e0ca9682","text":"Accelerated Computing","correct":false}]},{"id":"ab488ee0-acfc-4bf6-9b0a-832f6d99aeb3","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following AWS services is an example of Platform as a Service?","explanation":"Platform as a Service, or PaaS, enables the development, running, and management of applications on the cloud without the need to build and maintain an infrastructure. That is precisely what Elastic Beanstalk provides; it’s the ability to quickly deploy and manage applications in the AWS Cloud without worrying about the infrastructure that runs those applications. Elastic Beanstalk is the only PaaS listed here.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/elasticbeanstalk/","title":"AWS Elastic Beanstalk"}],"answers":[{"id":"270fcb785810d0206945029bb05f4e97","text":"Amazon S3","correct":false},{"id":"bcf6eb183b7da148701bcc059a34675f","text":"AWS Elastic Beanstalk","correct":true},{"id":"dee7ff8f7b10b9d388c7c561e9413b0d","text":"AWS Lambda","correct":false},{"id":"c33dcb724e4d74e54dbc8347d4402690","text":"Amazon Virtual Private Cloud","correct":false}]},{"id":"5fd1imv7-lqes-7e9n-vz33-eau71532v2ly","domain":"security","question":"How does AWS Shield Standard help protect your environment?","explanation":"AWS Shield Standard is included at no extra cost but will only block DDOS attacks on your AWS resources - it will not scan the contents of incoming or outgoing traffic (this is a function of WAF) and will not protect your environment from viruses","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/waf/latest/developerguide/shield-chapter.html","title":"AWS Shield"}],"answers":[{"id":"55063c26653acc06bd00cc13e1acc3a4","text":"By scanning your instances for viruses","correct":false},{"id":"3e6fc5c29a49e9d5c54bd4950ad5cbe0","text":"By scanning outgoing application traffic for sensitive information","correct":false},{"id":"b1d6309ddb9cc2f856af5a3bab83f37e","text":"By scanning incoming application traffic for know attacks","correct":false},{"id":"84009024e233c4995b00c514474f0ae5","text":"By Blocking DDOS attacks","correct":true}]},{"id":"6rxg9wr0-2vdy-xb2h-ds26-ul6n2c6g8bnu","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following support plans feature access to AWS support via email only during business hours?","explanation":"The Developer support plan features access to AWS support during business hours via email. Business and Enterprise support plans allow 24x7 email support. The Basic support plan includes no email support options. Because the question specifies support *only* during business hours, there is only one correct answer.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":true},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":false},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":false}]},{"id":"01355a86-1c9a-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"security","question":"In Amazon EC2, which of the following do you use to log into Linux instances?","explanation":"To log into Linux instances using EC2, you will need a key pair; Windows instances are the ones that need a user name and password to log in. Multi-factor authentication (MFA) involves the addition of an extra layer of protection, such as a code generated from an authenticator, to a user name and password. MFA can be enabled to use with IAM, or Identity and Access Management.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/introduction_security-outside-iam.html","title":"Security Features Outside of IAM"}],"answers":[{"id":"41dff7155cc7aeb11c06434f6a450bb3","text":"IAM","correct":false},{"id":"6cd56a4cc4ddbbfd2bc9d57de5d788aa","text":"Key pair","correct":true},{"id":"f3499a9f28ab4d9412f8dc5e818c8ccd","text":"User name and password","correct":false},{"id":"1a504cebc3822fd967eb6426a7ff0a31","text":"Multi-factor authentication","correct":false}]},{"id":"d7507bdc-1a47-11ea-9fef-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"What is the default limit for the number of network ACLs in a VPC?","explanation":"You can associate up to 200 network ACLs in each VPC.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/vpc/latest/userguide/amazon-vpc-limits.html","title":"Amazon VPC Limits"}],"answers":[{"id":"18d8042386b79e2c279fd162df0205c8","text":"400","correct":false},{"id":"3644a684f98ea8fe223c713b77189a77","text":"200","correct":true},{"id":"f899139df5e1059396431415e770c6dd","text":"100","correct":false},{"id":"94f6d7e04a4d452035300f18b984988c","text":"300","correct":false}]},{"id":"gz05o0zm-686t-arfr-tr1s-7wjbwyv832dv","domain":"tech","question":"You need to allow resources in a private subnet to access the internet. Which of the following must be present to enable this access?","explanation":"A NAT Gateway is required to allow resources in a private subnet to access the internet. Route tables tell traffic where it should go next to reach its destination, but don't actually process or transmit traffic. Security Groups and Network Access Control Lists are used to protect resources from traffic, and by themselves do not enable access to the internet - although they need to be properly configured to let traffic bound for the internet out.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonVPC/latest/UserGuide/vpc-nat-gateway.html","title":"About NAT Gateways"}],"answers":[{"id":"8ca0f1328403ec0d05ed995272d74715","text":"NAT Gateway","correct":true},{"id":"8f36276b8cef5979b167a77e143d894e","text":"Route Tables","correct":false},{"id":"06ea336ee4a57004a721e76f5cdd9083","text":"Network Access Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":false}]},{"id":"npfixa13-rww8-6ifs-mar3-1z12ny6vwzat","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following services will help you optimize your entire AWS environment in real-time following AWS best practices?","explanation":"Trusted Advisor helps you optimize your entire AWS environment in real-time following AWS best practices. It helps you optimize cost, fault-tolerance, and more.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/trustedadvisor/","title":"About Trusted Advisor"}],"answers":[{"id":"32685c9f0403b41381bf5f88788ad995","text":"AWS WAF","correct":false},{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":false},{"id":"05f43441d2d29ae2bb38fc8596ca6ff7","text":"AWS Trusted Advisor","correct":true},{"id":"7c90c8f2a24f3a1a28525f19fb2c75ab","text":"AWS Inspector","correct":false}]},{"id":"n7rouwfc-9cnc-mywz-rj44-v3c021ws4ry3","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following acts like built-in firewalls per instance for your virtual servers?","explanation":"Security Groups act like built-in firewalls for your virtual servers - the rules you create define what is allowed to talk to your instances and how. Although Network Access Control Lists can be used to block or deny traffic, these operate at the subnet level - covering all instances in the subnet with the same ruleset, not per-instance as the question specifies. Route tables tell traffic where it should go next to reach its destination, and an Availability Zone is a collection of datacentres - which isn't relevant in this question. ","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/using-network-security.html","title":"Amazon EC2 Security Groups"}],"answers":[{"id":"06ea336ee4a57004a721e76f5cdd9083","text":"Network Access Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":true},{"id":"1fb6aae6611aa5001c41c1e356609c41","text":"Availability Zones","correct":false},{"id":"8f36276b8cef5979b167a77e143d894e","text":"Route Tables","correct":false}]},{"id":"w5gffphd-hr0c-k6ie-54pn-4jmfwjc6h2bx","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the below are load balancer types that AWS offers?","explanation":"Valid load balancer types on AWS are Classic, Network and Application. Service, Web, Database and are not available types, however one of the valid types can be configured for these purposes.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/elasticloadbalancing/","title":"Elastic Load Balancing"}],"answers":[{"id":"d35b51b639528d580362ca7042de6a0e","text":"Classic","correct":true},{"id":"e498749f3c42246d50b15c81c101d988","text":"Application","correct":true},{"id":"eec89088ee408b80387155272b113256","text":"Network","correct":true},{"id":"e307db07b3975fef922a80d07455ee5e","text":"Database","correct":false},{"id":"0a52da7a03a6de3beefe54f8c03ad80d","text":"Original","correct":false},{"id":"c6e190b284633c48e39e55049da3cce8","text":"Web","correct":false},{"id":"c2ba7e785c49050f48da9aacc45c2b85","text":"Service","correct":false}]},{"id":"lzz1xk7l-o7hw-05ld-eq4w-bnnsryn338qb","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the below can be specified as an origin when creating a CloudFront distribution?","explanation":"A CloudFront Origin can be an S3 bucket, an Elastic Load Balancer, or a valid domain name.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonCloudFront/latest/DeveloperGuide/DownloadDistS3AndCustomOrigins.html","title":"CloudFront Origins"}],"answers":[{"id":"c0289d18d5fb07085b2755204da9008b","text":"A domain name","correct":true},{"id":"9cf4bd30d8e419d4586659b785653daf","text":"An S3 Bucket","correct":true},{"id":"c727fd87c3ae231f10b00f5df6719fdc","text":"An RDS instance","correct":false},{"id":"19c648650c3e65663a1edebcca84f065","text":"An ELB","correct":true}]},{"id":"ybx4uf1a-l9y3-aucn-tt1m-ku92d3hu5y5v","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are configuratble components of IAM?","explanation":"Users, Groups, Roles, and Permissions are integral to IAM. Authentication and Authorization are functions that IAM provides, but not actual components of it.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/iam/getting-started/","title":"IAM - Getting Started"}],"answers":[{"id":"18ade94f5fe966167a6645362290cdcb","text":"Authorizer","correct":false},{"id":"a37ede293936e29279ed543129451ec3","text":"Groups","correct":true},{"id":"f9aae5fda8d810a29f12d1e61b4ab25f","text":"Users","correct":true},{"id":"d08ccf52b4cdd08e41cfb99ec42e0b29","text":"Permissions","correct":true},{"id":"2999b7d01e6b02e94fc22c79b978d3b0","text":"Access controls","correct":false},{"id":"a5cd3ed116608dac017f14c046ea56bf","text":"Roles","correct":true},{"id":"3948d67c633d9035eaf2216ba0e1b2dc","text":"Authenticator","correct":false}]},{"id":"evaz1xrv-t8dc-4b8o-0z8b-k29mzh203trs","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following AWS Support levels offers the assistance of a Technical Account Manager?","explanation":"Only Enterprise (the highest level of Support Plan) offers the services of a Technical Account Manager.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":false},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"8d5e7e72f12067991186cdf3cb7d5d9d","text":"Premium","correct":false},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true}]},{"id":"9da21f94-7d9e-4bcf-8c7c-fc97b0634977","domain":"security","question":"Your company has updated its security policies to include cloud workloads as well as those running on-premises. Your manager would like a report of which technologies will require configuration changes. Which of the following will not be included in the report because they are the responsibility of AWS?","explanation":"In the AWS Shared Responsibility Model, AWS in responsible for managing host operating systems. Users are responsible for managing guest operating systems, as well as Security Group Firewalls, Amazon Aurora data encryption, and S3 access control lists.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"8061595e3a5f2fb2195dd627dd35f5d2","text":"Host operating systems","correct":true},{"id":"331bd4e2a8ab147e5a6a47e5b9c40d65","text":"S3 Access Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"64f8358ae4360eddd993acde2d19789c","text":"Amazon Aurora data encryption","correct":false},{"id":"63c21f07ff59add0f7e474ef5ec57c2e","text":"Security Group firewalls","correct":false}]},{"id":"afcc3e72-18ce-11ea-b8f0-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"If you want access to all AWS Trusted Advisor checks, which of these support plans will provide that?","explanation":"You must choose either the Business or Enterprise support plan to gain access to all AWS Trusted Advisor checks.","links":[{"url":"https://console.aws.amazon.com/support/plans/home?#/","title":"AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false}]},{"id":"57d67272-2fbd-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"What is the maximum amount of storage that Amazon Aurora offers?","explanation":"With each database instance launched in AWS, Aurora can auto-scale up to 64 TB when needed.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonRDS/latest/AuroraUserGuide/CHAP_AuroraOverview.html","title":"What Is Amazon Aurora?"}],"answers":[{"id":"c1edd650c09defc6ca8d0aaf67803ddc","text":"64 TB","correct":true},{"id":"911ede8df5585598c294830dafe276fa","text":"32 GB","correct":false},{"id":"074c2f1dacf9047766e7f8d5dce71060","text":"5 GB","correct":false},{"id":"70f79b00cb7649d94d473895d6c540d2","text":"1 TB","correct":false}]},{"id":"f119625a-2f3b-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Your Project Manager needs to know the daily spend of the company’s AWS account over the last 60 days to consider creating and implementing cost-effective measures. What should you do?","explanation":"Cost Explorer provides a trio of preconfigured views designed to quickly get you to common spends in your AWS environment. For viewing the daily spend over the last 60 days, your Project Manager needs to click the 'Daily Spend View' link. AWS Budgets is for generating automatic alerts when your AWS costs or usage exceed, or are forecasted to exceed, the thresholds you set; it is not for tracking your spend.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/billing-what-is.html","title":"What Is AWS Billing and Cost Management?"}],"answers":[{"id":"ae4dff5b9f90f7f36261f1743d9c6eb1","text":"Direct him to Monthly Spend by Linked Account View in AWS Cost Explorer.","correct":false},{"id":"e3963c15d2d033b249d8f75f4b7c05ff","text":"Direct him to AWS Budgets.","correct":false},{"id":"224e965acad73b5fc7fd31b503e947db","text":"Direct him to Daily Spend View in AWS Cost Explorer.","correct":true},{"id":"3061bd4594121d528b00ebc0b3cabd8b","text":"Direct him to Monthly Spend by Service View in AWS Cost Explorer.","correct":false}]},{"id":"1db22272-d476-4034-844a-5d8d9fd40091","domain":"concepts","question":"A telecommunications company has his hired you as a consultant to develop a business case for moving its IT applications and infrastructure to AWS. The company’s leadership understands the agility value of the cloud, but the finance group is not interested in shifting capital expense to operating expense due to the company’s tax structure. What will you include in the business case to attempt to satisfy everyone at the company?","explanation":"Many companies capitalize reserved instance purchases, especially those with 3-year terms. Waiting for current infrastructure to fully depreciate will cause the company to miss the other cloud benefits that are available. Moving the company to an operating expense model will prove too large a task, and will most likely result in a rejected business case. Elastic infrastructure is definitely a benefit, but doesn't address the capitalization issue.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/aws_pricing_overview.pdf","title":"How AWS Pricing Works"}],"answers":[{"id":"8419aa56459afcd14644026053cc0cfc","text":"Show the company the TCO value of moving to an operating expense model","correct":false},{"id":"b55403f80a04df0f30d6552d35188c46","text":"Suggest that the company wait to migrate to AWS until the current infrastructure is fully depreciated","correct":false},{"id":"cd56c0654f075d81e563f7f6740b2cb8","text":"Show the value of an elastic infrastructure for avoiding wasted capacity","correct":false},{"id":"875be7dcedf2167b7fa3192f4c94b2a3","text":"Suggest that the company make reserved instance purchases and capitalize them","correct":true}]},{"id":"smnrxkfv-dk56-snvh-i93e-or0vfomvccbz","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are characteristics of cloud computing?","explanation":"The on-demand delivery via the internet of services with pay-as-you-go pricing characterizes cloud computing. Services incurred from a cloud services provider are operating expenses, not capital expenses. Capital Expenditure (CAPEX) is less common with the cloud, in favour of Operational Expenditure (OPEX). Skills and training for personnel are required to leverage Cloud Computing","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/what-is-cloud-computing/","title":"What is Cloud Computing?"}],"answers":[{"id":"481f1c72f1007c1ac8e4a484b47af4f2","text":"Cloud charges are Capital Expenditures.","correct":false},{"id":"9b670633c5238ca5a17dd651c3a63662","text":"No extra skills or training are required.","correct":false},{"id":"2b34d3fef0b313e0047a2557d9842378","text":"Pay-as-you-go pricing","correct":true},{"id":"ebc744edbd870e96fe9e680b407ad053","text":"On-demand delivery","correct":true},{"id":"dcfe379beaf88dbe9d59e7fcecf6f98a","text":"Services are delivered via the Internet.","correct":true}]},{"id":"q9rl4dzm-8wyq-y23f-41wx-15rhrz976akb","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are a collection of datacentres within a specific region?","explanation":"Availability Zones are a collection of datacentres within a specific region.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"2bdbf4724b81ff0529e32fdb1af28130","text":"AWS Origins","correct":false},{"id":"5948f3347ebc02ebc690227c059661e1","text":"Regions","correct":false},{"id":"17d8fc1e4ceb765476776889d7f6c5ab","text":"Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"1fb6aae6611aa5001c41c1e356609c41","text":"Availability Zones","correct":true}]},{"id":"cckhl0ep-pmhf-g8be-yplb-dzr17jgnk6mn","domain":"security","question":"Where is the best place to store your Root User Access Key so that your application can use it to make requests to AWS?","explanation":"It is not recommended to use Root User account or access keys for any reason as these grant full unrestricted access to the entire account. Recommended practice is to follow the concept of \"Least Privilege\" and create am IAM user or role with just enough access to do what is needed and nothing more, and use those keys as required","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/general/latest/gr/aws-access-keys-best-practices.html","title":"Best Practices for Managing AWS Access Keys"}],"answers":[{"id":"503d72b0254a8561511b71a95f8eb8a7","text":"It should be configured as a parameter and held in the Key Management Store (KMS)","correct":false},{"id":"2330278fe444dd9a6196cb146c97de7e","text":"Nowhere - you should not use the Root User access keys for this","correct":true},{"id":"73532a5c24d7b4c1df276690bbaedfff","text":"In the .aws file in you application","correct":false},{"id":"9feb4a526584eae16c38880b7813f48c","text":"It needs to be coded directly into your application","correct":false}]},{"id":"a87b87a1-e801-e917-756a-a78256b2945c","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following is a Shared Control of the AWS Shared Responsibility Model?","explanation":"Shared Controls are elements of the Shared Responsibility Model where both AWS and the customer have shared responsibilities within their own contexts. Awareness & Training is a Shared Control, since AWS trains AWS employees, but a customer must train their own employees. Datacentre Security is solely the responsibility of AWS. Configuration of an Application within an EC2 instance, and Identity and Access Management remain the responsibility of the customer","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"e40133007bfa03149696a52e6c45b8d9","text":"EC2 Instance Application Configuration","correct":false},{"id":"4fde53f82fbc6748a0e6b9b51f615287","text":"Datacentre Security","correct":false},{"id":"791716f366839a73d41b8ac1ae95bad0","text":"Identity and Access Management","correct":false},{"id":"027e815b818f136c5892cd32b9f87ddd","text":"Awareness & Training","correct":true}]},{"id":"wdqr2l66-jcd9-o6lx-b012-qodibilagwi2","domain":"tech","question":"You need to implement an automated service that will scan your AWS environment with the goal of both improving security and reducing costs. Which service should you use?","explanation":"An online resource to help you reduce cost, increase performance, and improve security by optimizing your AWS environment, Trusted Advisor provides real-time guidance to help you provision your resources following AWS best practices.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/trustedadvisor/","title":"About Trusted Advisor"}],"answers":[{"id":"92fbbd5478621cf8f70624389759b44c","text":"CloudTrail","correct":false},{"id":"9633b701743bf40ce928fb9fa4c0ed66","text":"Config Rules","correct":false},{"id":"739749e0ec278613ef4f8e6861efc722","text":"Trusted Advisor","correct":true},{"id":"0bcfa28115476b2bcfed146f27c465c4","text":"Service Catalog","correct":false}]},{"id":"cd40e670-2ffc-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following statements is true of AWS Elastic Beanstalk?","explanation":"With Elastic Beanstalk, you can quickly deploy and manage web applications in the AWS Cloud without having to learn about the infrastructure that runs them. That’s what makes it a Platform as a Service. There is no charge for using Elastic Beanstalk itself; you are only charged for the underlying AWS resources that the application uses.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/elasticbeanstalk/latest/dg/Welcome.html","title":"What is AWS Elastic Beanstalk?"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/types-of-cloud-computing/","title":"Types of Cloud Computing"}],"answers":[{"id":"6efc4ed7a174b46c2ecebb016e0329eb","text":"It is Platform as a Service (PaaS).","correct":true},{"id":"20fb5a0ca00f262eed3b067bb1718e82","text":"There is a charge for using Elastic Beanstalk.","correct":false},{"id":"0e2daa2a54c9f6d95ceebc8b65589f62","text":"It enables you to quickly deploy and manage web applications in the cloud.","correct":true},{"id":"2d4a6743e5521dc61e99fdb14ee7f4b1","text":"It is Software as a Service (SaaS).","correct":false}]},{"id":"1bq7soel-r0fa-9nu9-nkn7-tsl4tdqsb4ne","domain":"security","question":"You would like to give an application running on one of your EC2 instances access to an S3 bucket - what is the best way to implement this?","explanation":"The recommended method to assign permissions to apps running in EC2 is to use IAM roles. Making the bucket public could work, but will also expose all the data to the internet and is not secure. The other methods are also less secure than using IAM roles and are not recommended in this case.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/best-practices.html","title":"IAM Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"6d5604611f5103e032eae843cc2d3861","text":"Give the application a set of Access Keys","correct":false},{"id":"1e3f1e527016bc7fae2856f9acfd533a","text":"Assign the instance an IAM role","correct":true},{"id":"200bfcc1caf00feb47c6ca792e965a17","text":"Make the bucket public","correct":false},{"id":"506f9dca07627c4a0037801fd015ae25","text":"Use an IAM user for the application","correct":false}]},{"id":"ej2zjxm0-a6xk-q2af-mol8-3c9zwje8qxyh","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following support plans features a < 4-hour response time in the event of an impaired production system?","explanation":"Both the Business and Enterprise support levels offer a < 4-hour response time in the event of an impaired production system. Developer is < 12-hour response time in case of any system impairment. Basic does not offer any support for system impairment. Individual is not a real support plan","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"2dd4472245a696bc0b4b944db2a8b519","text":"Individual","correct":false},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false}]},{"id":"0e20ce8c-1a57-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following statements is true of AWS Regions?","explanation":"AWS Regions are geographical areas that consist of locations called Availability Zones. Because they are isolated from each other, there is no automatic replication of resources between them. In addition, data transfer between Regions is not free; there is a charge associated with that.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/using-regions-availability-zones.html","title":"Regions, Availability Zones, and Local Zones"}],"answers":[{"id":"f941bbe63c60384543e03468d67e8a94","text":"They are independent geographical areas.","correct":true},{"id":"96676b55f4ae2e27083b81e373c80e5a","text":"They automatically replicate resources among each other.","correct":false},{"id":"6f99c65ce03a0a9018c608fc49149883","text":"There are no charges for data transferred between them.","correct":false},{"id":"3a4116551c9039850c094ec59ecc726c","text":"They are composed of Availability Zones.","correct":true}]},{"id":"7b242f9e-5541-40b9-94c3-ff760252f026","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following scenarios are examples of scaling an IT architecture vertically?","explanation":"To scale vertically is to increase the specifications of a single AWS resource as needed. For example, resizing EC2 or RDS instances for more CPU, memory, or network capabilities is scaling vertically. Adding more EC2 or RDS instances, on the other hand, is scaling horizontally because it involves the increase in the number of resources, rather than the increase in each resource’s capabilities.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"67c96e88044c732523807882de714af3","text":"Adding two more RDS instances","correct":false},{"id":"4fd553484e87f00281d8e2d07df1c3ac","text":"Resizing an EC2 instance type from a1.medium to a1.xlarge for more CPU and memory power","correct":true},{"id":"d2ed8876ad5d876850ebcde76e28bd9f","text":"Adding two more EC2 instances","correct":false},{"id":"f9de222cea376a61a621e215c4daf0dc","text":"Resizing an RDS instance type from db.r5.large to db.r5.2xlarge","correct":true}]},{"id":"h0bz8vyv-zk25-7xf6-p1l3-v0qntk7m5yjw","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are types of cloud computing deployments?","explanation":"The three types of cloud deployments are: \r\n Public - where everyone and anyone can access that cloud's resources \r\n Private - also called on-premises where the underlying cloud infrastructure is owned and operated by a private entity for the sole use of that entity \r\n Hybrid - which is a mix of both. \r\n Mixed cloud is not a term used to describe a cloud computing deployment","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/types-of-cloud-computing/","title":"Types of Cloud Computing"}],"answers":[{"id":"cb38b39495aded16d3565297386a9c9e","text":"Private cloud","correct":true},{"id":"2dde6ce98c19e445f3c47a7a9d166f04","text":"Hybrid cloud","correct":true},{"id":"761883c0d5c55fba5b200ac8ac0d86e5","text":"Public cloud","correct":true},{"id":"7d22e2d665f6d51244a33f26e96904f9","text":"Mixed cloud","correct":false}]},{"id":"065786b4-2fbf-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following is an advantage of using Amazon Aurora over MySQL and PostgreSQL?","explanation":"Aurora, which is Amazon’s very own relational database service (RDS) offering, is capable of delivering up to five times the throughput of MySQL and up to three times the throughput of PostgreSQL, therefore it is a faster RDS engine than MySQL and PostgresSQL. The other responses are not correct because all three database engines are supported in AWS RDS, provide high availability, and can auto-scale their storage capabilities.","links":[{"url":" https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonRDS/latest/AuroraUserGuide/CHAP_AuroraOverview.html","title":"What Is Amazon Aurora?"}],"answers":[{"id":"69b1cc807abf4ac85af0b5fd99275f27","text":"Unlike MySQL and PostgresSQL, Aurora can auto-scale in storage.","correct":false},{"id":"b0e9556359058a92983935d53f8dd9ac","text":" Unlike MySQL and PostgreSQL, Aurora can be used with AWS Relational Database Service (RDS).","correct":false},{"id":"fe74accc7d3b87bf524b103b8501463c","text":"Unlike MySQL and PostgreSQL, Aurora is highly available.","correct":false},{"id":"2af45970d86937f0ee6307f5f1d7f1e8","text":"Aurora is faster than MySQL and PostgreSQL.","correct":true}]},{"id":"nfy6hmhv-trpt-lh3v-z6zh-4icv8kpv7xn6","domain":"concepts","question":"When setting up an Organization in AWS, which of the below is true when selecting which features to enable?","explanation":"With AWS Organizations, Consolidated Billing is always enabled. All other features are either enabled as a group, or disabled as a group - that is, you cannot individually enable or disable a feature - it's all or nothing!","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/en_pv/organizations/latest/userguide/orgs_getting-started_concepts.html","title":"AWS Organizations Terminology and Concepts"}],"answers":[{"id":"125540f5091c07ae2a9b7b8c0d95a432","text":"You can select to have just Consolidated Billing enabled","correct":true},{"id":"fd07b14b5f6a4065154c418c232ecd89","text":"You can select to have Consolidated Billing disabled, then pick which of the other features you want enabled.","correct":false},{"id":"ea31b0ef93ed02b05984774a32d72054","text":"You can select to have Consolidated Billing, then pick which other individual features you want enabled ","correct":false},{"id":"4890bb732d34952682735fd4950bcae8","text":"You can select to have Consolidated Billing, plus all other features enabled","correct":true}]},{"id":"ff57921e-2faa-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following statements are true of the AWS Free Tier?","explanation":"All statements listed here are correct except for one. If you don’t use all your Free Tier benefits within the month, they don’t roll over to the next month.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/billing-free-tier.html","title":"Using the AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"8723f65debe98902ae71daeac7ca33e0","text":"Upon creation of an AWS account, the user is automatically signed up for the Free Tier for 12 months.","correct":true},{"id":"e0a5844f80154f67479f312499e75d1a","text":"Usage must be kept below the Free Tier limits to avoid charges.","correct":true},{"id":"aec630c6387bfee54b18d0ca80ea994c","text":"Unused benefits that the Free Tier provides in a given month roll over to the next month.","correct":false},{"id":"fca0d4d0e7ba8ff0a86efa806423c98d","text":"AWS starts charging the regular rates for usage of services and resources when the Free Tier expires.","correct":true}]},{"id":"j55neiwz-9leq-mmdm-z3qb-rjp9ll7te3ey","domain":"tech","question":"By default, what can a Private Subnet communicate with?","explanation":"By default, a Private Subnet can only communicate with other subnets in the same VPC, be they Private or Public. In order to communicate to the internet, a NAT Gateway and Internet Gateway are required, and to enable communication between subnets in different VPCs the VPCs must first be peered.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonVPC/latest/UserGuide/VPC_Subnets.html#vpc-subnet-basics","title":"VPC and Subnet Basics"}],"answers":[{"id":"bc073365b9c1fbd0626a854e3b600009","text":"The internet","correct":false},{"id":"fc10601fc9c6d89cc325196b308a5d09","text":"Public Subnets in a different VPC","correct":false},{"id":"2833f376428e487505135ddd3e3dfa83","text":"Other Private Subnets in the same VPC","correct":true},{"id":"6aff3455ef4ee9f91852d846278af179","text":"Private Subnets in a different VPC","correct":false},{"id":"8d6c6a7fbfb26a46f1cb21637cb6efc6","text":"Public Subnets in the same VPC","correct":true}]},{"id":"7a194fa6-5966-4548-9b32-ac602a517ac8","domain":"concepts","question":"With AWS services, you can use as many resources as you need, as well as use them when you need them. Which of the following terms can be applied to this concept?","explanation":"Working in a traditional infrastructure environment means that you have to deal with fixed resources, which is comparatively costly and labor-intensive. By contrast, AWS services are much more convenient; the services provide the ability to use as many resources as you need and dispose of them when you no longer need them. That’s why such resources are both temporary and disposable.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"e035a6f9ed7c8c3c99e48b95e32cc364","text":"Fixed resources","correct":false},{"id":"fd3ca13906a4c1e05f791d27dbc66914","text":"Disposable resources","correct":true},{"id":"5936fc4450b6f3f75cc6fe08d2890b77","text":"Temporary resources","correct":true},{"id":"83ec702ebd8e13f87318dba136356773","text":"Dedicated resources","correct":false}]},{"id":"e915ef52-2be6-4fba-8d62-b668f639c29a","domain":"billing","question":"To stay within the AWS Free Tier using Amazon EC2 for the first 12 months of having an AWS account, which of the following instance types should you use?","explanation":"One of the EC2 requirements for staying within the AWS Free Tier is using EC2 micro instances only. While the other instance types can be cheap, only t2.micro is eligibile for free tier usage","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/free/?all-free-tier.sort-by=item.additionalFields.SortRank&all-free-tier.sort-order=asc","title":"AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"ab61127647912c159c3fc08e9a102efc","text":"t2.small","correct":false},{"id":"cc114cafeb511c9cbe6666312f54a8de","text":"m5.medium","correct":false},{"id":"05c25e549fbb3f158f12a9945bff38ee","text":"t3.medium","correct":false},{"id":"1d4f2c610dbeb44e7ba09fed19564c76","text":"t2.micro","correct":true}]},{"id":"fd9d7891-1f20-431b-81e8-091169615548","domain":"tech","question":"Your sales operations group would like to perform monthly analyses on large amounts of sales activity. They want to be able to rank the performance of different territories, product categories, and sales channels. They will use visualization tools to generate graphical representations of the data. Which AWS service will provide the best solution for storing the sales data?","explanation":"Amazon Redshift provides the best solution for performing queries based on a predefined set of dimensions. Redshift organizes data for high performance based on user-specified distribution schemes. Amazon ElastiCache provides in-memory performance, but no data organization assistance. Amazon Aurora and Amazon DynamoDB are good solutions, but Redshift's columnar storage gives it the edge.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/redshift/?nc2=h_m1","title":"Amazon Redshift"}],"answers":[{"id":"ecafbaed9f41dac736e496a7cd234ce4","text":"Amazon DynamoDB","correct":false},{"id":"770b120ec487568871cc9ab64475af46","text":"Amazon ElastiCache","correct":false},{"id":"f7415e33f972c03abd4f3fed36748f7a","text":"Amazon Redshift","correct":true},{"id":"69670a9d53817d1ec89e685997343ce2","text":"Amazon Aurora","correct":false}]},{"id":"trwylx1o-zl9g-9de6-rxeg-gp4pakkifop1","domain":"tech","question":"The load on your application fluctuates by day of the week. Wednesdays have the most traffic; Saturdays have the least traffic. Which AWS service allows you to ensure you have the correct amount of compute capacity while also optimizing on a cost basis? ","explanation":"Auto Scaling allows you to add or remove EC2 instances based on conditions you specify. Auto-Scaling events can be scheduled to meet predictable changes in the load on your application.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/autoscaling/","title":"About Auto Scaling"}],"answers":[{"id":"afd14eb3f151c84e6ef7ab63812b4fbc","text":"Auto Scaling","correct":true},{"id":"311bdda432aba736b8dcb987523c0c92","text":"CloudWatch","correct":false},{"id":"a2c64f657687c46ed9811761849051e4","text":"EC2 Container Service","correct":false},{"id":"739749e0ec278613ef4f8e6861efc722","text":"Trusted Advisor","correct":false}]},{"id":"nncwnx24-taau-zgsd-blel-newfprz6u93i","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are principles of sound design when it comes to security?","explanation":"The AWS Cloud includes many design patterns and architectural options that you can apply to a wide variety of use cases. Some key design principles of sound design when it comes to security include: Apply security to all layers, enable tracability, and implement the principal of least privlidge options.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/apn/the-5-pillars-of-the-aws-well-architected-framework/","title":"The 5 Pillars of the AWS Well-Architected Framework"}],"answers":[{"id":"ff94370d49b79e8817f49bbbc97dbf02","text":"Apply security to your application only.","correct":false},{"id":"214beb729ce64f08fe84798c5bbedd6f","text":"Enable traceability.","correct":true},{"id":"d0f7903229df2e315b9c9561f18a4b7c","text":"Secure your physical resources.","correct":false},{"id":"4bb4d3eefe3829a2b20a099180702f9f","text":"Apply security at all layers.","correct":true},{"id":"718831eabf7a4582f906032cd06bcea7","text":"Implement the Principle of Least Privilege","correct":true}]},{"id":"e08137aa-20a0-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following describes a subnet?","explanation":"A virtual private cloud, or VPC, is the virtual network you create in your AWS account. When you create a VPC, you split it into smaller network segments by specifying a range of IP addresses. These segments are referred to as subnets, and this is where you launch your AWS resources.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/vpc/latest/userguide/what-is-amazon-vpc.html","title":"What Is Amazon VPC?"}],"answers":[{"id":"35b8947d693a814719c463b699fee868","text":"A subsection of the Internet","correct":false},{"id":"79da4a3447f86eaa72f611a8d8a1d4cc","text":"A private connection to the virtual private cloud","correct":false},{"id":"341f92e23cc01405941735e106cc5b82","text":"A range of IP addresses in the virtual private cloud","correct":true},{"id":"5e57bdce4ee3d720c44022ab3a1989dc","text":"A virtual network dedicated to an AWS account","correct":false}]},{"id":"8dmul9q1-wi30-bo4k-81j9-ztcv7dgeoybt","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following EC2 instance types will realize a savings over time in exchange for a contracted term-of-service?","explanation":"EC2 Reserved Instances offer significant discounts for a contracted term-of-service, of up to 75% off. On-Demand instances are charged equally per-hour, regardless of how long they're run for. Spot instances are cheaper than On-Demand instances, but aren't intended for long term use","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"bcc129e8d9496a05a331c903d4c5bcb0","text":"Reserved instances","correct":true},{"id":"409aa157dda2d7faab6bf2938e322891","text":"Discount instances","correct":false},{"id":"991236e27b7cb98a2eeff8897b3e0bb4","text":"Spot instances","correct":false},{"id":"2a80e91907ea76d424690185914b6eae","text":"On-demand instances","correct":false}]},{"id":"520b9022-2fa7-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Your company needs the support of concierge-level account specialists to help with billing and account subjects. Which of the following AWS Support pricing plans provides that feature?","explanation":"Only the Enterprise support plan will provide a Concierge Support Team, which is a group of account specialists to assist your company with their billing and accounting questions.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/","title":"AWS Support Plans"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/enterprise/","title":"AWS Enterprise Support"}],"answers":[{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":false},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true}]}]}}}}
